ATENA RAZM

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

A Software Developer with +2 years of experience bringing forth a true passion for design and a knack for problem-solving. Worked on web and mobile games and applications using Unity, C#, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, React, NextJs, React Native, Redux, and backend languages and services like PHP, Laravel. Committed to responsive design and high-quality deliverables, and capable of using the tools and software like Jenkins, PlayFab, Git, Perforce, VSC, Jira, Figma to build, test, and deploy a product. Bringing strong communication and team lead skills to the table due to my Hospitality and Business background. Mentoring students in CS Dojo Vancouver Community.

SELECTED PROJECTS

Check out more projects on my Portfolio Website

LevelUp Game

PLAY | CODE BASE | BLOG

A 3D game created on Unity using C#, Unity Physics, Assets, Prefabs, Particle System, and Audio System.

Hatchways Student Assessment

LINK | CODE BASE | BLOG

This project is done with React & Redux, and represents my knowledge and skills of working with APIs, HTTP protocol and web browsers, manipulating the fetched data and displaying them with the given UI design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer.

PIP Empire

Mar 2024 - Present

- Using React, NextJS, and Tailwind to create reusable UI components from the provided UX/UI design.
- Participating in code reviews, debugging, and completing the technical documentation.

Software Engineer (Volunteer)

GoodBot

Feb 2024 - Present

- Implement an input system to save user data in the database via API calls using React and NextJS.
- Assist the UX design team in redesigning an MVP web application.

Associate Software Engineer

East Side Games Studio

May 2021 - Aug 2023

- Implemented logic to existing components to improve the performance as the User's ID Copy-to-Clipboard feature, the dialog popup calling frequency cooldown, and calling an internal failsafe method automation by checking the backend hit-points.
- Performed pair programming to figure out the architecture of a newly handed Unity project, accepted UX/UI design mock-ups, and developed the UI of the "Delete Account" feature by creating new Prefabs.
- Safely integrated new technologies, updated dependencies, and replaced SDKs and third-party libraries.
- Removed unwanted components from the UI, and debugged various UI problems like the missing animations, the Audio reset bug and image overlaps.
- Initiated research and conducted usability and playtesting to identify the potential areas for player retention improvement. Collected and condensed the data and provided the documentation to the CEO.
- Worked with existing codebase consisting of Asset Bundles, Game Layout and positioning, Game Events, Animation, and Input Systems on Mobile and Steam.

EDUCATION

British Columbia Institute of Technology (BCIT)

Applied Web Development - Associate Certificate

European University of Yerevan

MBA

Tehran Institute of Technology

Hospitality & Hotel Management - Bachelor's degree